# Ing. Pavel Šťastný

Tel.: 732 109 749



#### Who am I

I am a person who tries to work on himself, gain experience and constantly learn. I am curious and I like to try things on my own. I would like a good front-end developer, since that is the field I am interested in. Programming is my passion. My strengths are fast learning and purposefulness. My weakness is stubbornness. I am kind of an optimist and something between an extrovert and an introvert.

## **Education**

2017-2020: **ESF MU Brno** - Master's full-time study

field: **Economics. Graduation**: January 2020, degree: Ing.

Masarykova univerzita Ekonomicko-správní fakulta

2014-2017 ESF MU Brno – Bachelor's full-time study

field: Economics. Graduation: 2017, degree: Bc.

## **Experience**

## Front-end developer at Brandmaster s.r.o. (2021/07 - present)

Job duties:

- Development of internal web applications and custom web apps for customers.
- Technologies: JS, CSS/SCSS, HTML, PUG, GIT, Angular, Gulp

## UX/UI developer at Visitpro.eu (part-time) (2021/03 - present)

Job duties:

- Coding of UI elements, UX development, the overall styling of application.
- Technologies: SCSS, GIT, Blazor, Next.JS

## Software tester at TwinSoft s.r.o (2017/11 - 2021/07)

Job duties:

- Manual and automated testing of a web application.
- Work with SQL database (queries, data management).
- Communication with clients. Cooperation during development UX/UI, problem-solving.
- Presentation of the software to the clients. Writing methodological help for clients.

#### Hard skills

- HTML, CSS, JavaScript
- React, Angular, see portfolio
- SQL basic queries
- English C1/B2
- French—B2/B1













#### Soft skills

- Team worker more heads know more
- Effective communication speaking is silver...
- **Independence** –I solve problems by myself first
- Fast-learner I can learn quickly
- **Creativity** that is "playing intelligence"

## More about me

Since I have always been interested in web development, I started to study this subject after my master's degree. At that time, I was still employed as a SW tester. After finishing courses for web dev (can be seen on my web portfolio), I found a part-time job as UX/UI developer in local company. A few months later, I found a full-time job as a front-end developer. And then I knew that I did not want to do anything else.

My web portfolio: https://paulicz44.github.io/stastnypavel.github.io/